kitefly.in 2018-12-16

# Privacy Policy

### Privacy Policy

Please read below to learn more about our Privacy Policy. Your use of the Website is subject to this Privacy Policy, as well as our Terms of Service and Community Guidelines.

#### Information We Collect and Use

kitefly collects information from you when you register on the Website, when you use kitefly products or services, and when you visit any kitefly pages.

When you register on the Website, you may be asked to enter your name, e-mail address, gender, date of birth, location, and other personal details about yourself. All of this data, except your gender and your date of birth, can be edited by you at any time thereafter. kitefly automatically receives and records information from your browser, including your IP address, kitefly cookie information, and the pages you request, on our server logs.

Google, as a third party vendor, relies on user cookies to display ads on our site. Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to display ads to users based on their visit to our Website and others. Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy.

#### What Do We Do With Your Personal Data?

We may use the information we collect from you in one or more of the following ways:

  * Publish the information intended to be made public by you, under the conditions specified in your Settings;
  * Allow you to properly use the Website, under the conditions specified in your Settings;
  * Send you communication about the Website, as well as our other products and services;
  * Provide you with advertisements tailored to your profile;
  * Investigate fraud and infringements of our Community Guidelines; and
  * Improve customer service based on your feedback and experiences. 

#### Do We Use Cookies?

Yes. Cookies are small files that, with your allowance, a site or its service provider transfers to your computer’s hard drive through your Web browser. They enable the site’s or service provider’s systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information that allows for ease of future use. For instance, we use cookies to understand and save your preferences for future visits.

#### Do We Disclose Any Information to Outside Parties?

Third parties can access all information made public by you, under the conditions specified in your privacy Settings. 

Your personal data and/or e-mail address will never be sold or transferred to any other company for any reason whatsoever, without your knowledge or consent. We do reserve the right to provide legal authorities with your information in cases of illegal activity on the Website.

#### How Do We Protect Your Information?

We implement a variety of industry standard security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information, such as data encryption and utilizing a secure socket layer for payment transactions. Keeping your data secure is something we take very seriously.

#### Communication from kitefly

We may contact you via e-mail with service-related notifications and announcements. With the exception of essential account-related e-mails, you may opt out of all e-mail communication from kitefly on your Settings page. Non-members may block all e-mail communication from kitefly by clicking the one-click Unsubscribe link found in the footer of any e-mails sent to non-members.

#### Third-Party Links

Occasionally, at our discretion, we may include or offer third-party products or services on our Website. These third-party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about your experiences with these sites.

#### Google User Data

When you search for friends on kitefly, you may authenticate with your Google account and permit us to read your contacts. This information will be used for the sole purpose of connecting you with your friends already on kitefly, or inviting them to it. We will never share this information with third parties. Should you choose to invite your contacts, you can do so in an opt-in manner.

#### Inviting Friends

When you search for friends or invite friends on kitefly, you may be asked to provide your friends’ names, email addresses, and/or mobile phone numbers. By clicking a button or link such as "Find friends," "Add friends", "Show contacts", or other such button or link text that signals your interest, you give kitefly permission to import your address book contacts, including names, e-mail addresses, and phone numbers, and to store these data indefinitely. If you then choose to send invitations to these contacts, we will use this information to send people you select a message and/or SMS text message on your behalf using your name, photo, e-mail address and/or mobile phone number. We may also send a limited number of reminders to them in your name. Your information will be stored in a safe and secure manner. We will make no other use of this information for any other marketing purposes without notification.

#### Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance

We are in full compliance with the requirements of Children's Online Privacy Protection Act (COPPA). We do not collect any information from anyone under 13 years of age. Our website, products, and services are all directed towards and meant for use by people who are at least 18 years of age or older.

#### Online Privacy Policy Only

This online Privacy Policy applies only to information collected through our Website and not to information collected offline. 

#### Your Consent

By using our site, you consent to our Website’s Privacy Policy.

#### Changes to our Privacy Policy

kitefly reserves the right, at its sole discretion, to modify or replace any part of this Privacy Policy. If we decide to change our Privacy Policy, we will post those changes on this page. It is your responsibility to check this Policy periodically for changes. Your continued use of or access to the Website following the posting of any changes constitutes acceptance of those changes.
